exercise uh-huh my arms better now so I'll walk on days I don't have cram school and you don't
leave early so then that means you'll be able to walk home with me every day just the two of us
uh um I mean I basically already am and double riding on my bike is too risky
she's a celebrity there would be no coming back from getting in trouble oh that reminds me um
hold this for a sec let's see there's my udon point card my test I got a 52 on money for a
signboard for graduation what is this a scrap paper maker
nationwide special admission ticket
what's a gift the star of the movie Yuko Kitamura is from the same agency as me
it's almost ending its run in theaters so I figure I gotta go today or I'll miss it
still looking for something huh no a love story huh oh
oh uh Moeko gave me this ribbon for when I go out somewhere after school
what's up with your card again why am I wearing this
you look grown up this way what's that mean
there's the other ticket that's where it was oh here's this back
you can have this oh thanks don't that's not what this means
um see ya what do you want
uh um wanna go or like I can maybe go see it with you if you like
yeah of course
sorry for what um you know for making you ask me
it's fine it feels like I really followed my heart with that move today
you like you want a date careful there's always traps
nothing just my own heart fighting against itself
you should unbutton it like this
I got us out of double riding but it still feels like we're doing something bad
out here like this we're like high schoolers like we skipped a few grades
if I run into anyone I know out here I'll just explode
probably think I'm some big show-off
oh looky let's get something to eat
okay time to go stealth mode snake-like
excuse me hi what can I get
no we're just like going to see a movie that's it sounds like a definite yes to
me oh wow you work here yeah you can order or what
we'll eat inside hang on just wait a second now
this is just me talking to myself what even if I were to win the heart of some
beautiful Arabian oil prince and win myself unlimited wealth and power
there is one thing I would never have and that is
an after-school date in my school uniform
you chew on that bro keep this up and I'll give you a one-star review sis
I think it's fine to wear your uniform on a date as an adult
don't bother punching back
wait is this a date what are you doing that's not even close
I'm sorry I think she's in trouble
don't stare she used to practice at home every day when she first started
yeah that is some commitment well it is her job and all
eat up be insatiable and never let him dish out more than you can consume
right stop
hey look who's trying to look cool now
enough already
yeah yeah okay
to be totally honest with you
takoyaki isn't really my thing
what you picked this place
I mean I do like it
make up your mind then
I'm sorry I'm just really bad at eating them
which is why they're not my favorite
don't stuff the whole thing in your mouth then
sorry for the wait here are your drinks
so now who's the one staring
huh no it's just I've never really seen someone that's close to me at work like this
just thought she's working hard
yeah
huh
well um I have a photo shoot next Sunday for a magazine
you could come see me if you want
see her at work
I'd be in the way
it's outside so it's fine
I mean I think
I'll go if I can
okay
that means you won't show up at all
that's only when adults say it to each other
so that means
I don't mind going to see
I'm definitely interested
but still
yippee
is this last one
mine
it is
thanks
you should cool the inside first
you do it
seriously
first you split it open like this
excuse me
go right ahead
what am I even doing
wait
one cheese
really
and one spring onion
your bill
come on I got it covered
what really
you sure
cut me a little slack
you're getting yelled at by the newbie
shut up and scram
they call me popcorn man
uh
hello
that thing's huge
I mean even for you
we're gonna share it
a date
if going out to do something alone with a girl
is what people call a date
then I guess this is one
assuming this is a date
it kind of feels like going too far though
huh
hey
let's swap seats yeah
why
no reason
you watch movies a lot
no
not at the theater at least
and I fall asleep watching them at home
I'll wake you up if you do
you know
the movie you're going to be in
I read the book that it's based on
wow
you remembered that
it was already on my radar anyway
your character isn't in the book though
they aren't
you haven't read it
I'm having to go to Hiroshima to film for that movie you know
over spring break for about a week
yeah
this movie today is to help me study acting
and Yuko Kitamura is the actress I want to be like most
you know what I mean
the cool roles
the funny ones
she's amazing at everything
guess even Yamada talks fast
when it's about something she likes
this feeling I get when it comes to her work
is hard for me to try and describe
the movie will begin momentarily
please enjoy
want me to tell mom you'll be out late
shut your face
huh
wait
this reminds me of another movie
no
I think I might be the werewolf
Nioh Werewolf
last final two
a movie with Lemon Zaka
or whatever
from half a year ago
why did I watch it
because the credits listed Anna Akino
which meant Yamada was in it
huh
shoot
where was I
what a bunch of losers acting all scared like that
she played some random mean girl who died super early on
but you could see the difference between her and an amateur clear as day
you could tell she's an actress
wake up
I wasn't sleeping
huh
a kiss scene
and a long one
this is so awkward
wow
Yamada sees the world through different eyes
I'm always reminded of that fact
and scared by it
but even still
their love didn't work out
but I have to believe breakups don't always have to be bad
and Yuka Kitamura was just so pretty up there like that
oh sorry
for what
just feels like it probably wasn't your type of movie
but
even still
I'm afraid that
I've been rambling all day about stuff I like
even still
seeing her rave about things I'll never know
is a beauty to behold
I wanna
huh
know you
much better
I just never knew you were so into studying this stuff
oh
um
yeah
I learned a lot today
from the movie I mean
outside of work as well
apple
eraser
ramen rope
uniform
milk tea
abacus
stew
worm
matsutake
emblem
ma
merci
in
yay
I lost
I win
I'm the winner
hey
what's up
do I look weird
in this
nope
looks good
thanks
uh
it's so early
I'm gonna get a look at Yamada at work today
I took her at her word that it was okay to come
but is it really
is this weird
oh right
times like these
call for little gifts I think
if it's weird I just won't give it to her
thank you
that's sunday morning for you
there's no one here
I stick out like a sore thumb
I wanted to blend in with the crowd while I watched
hmm
oh
you're sure looking cute today Anna
what
I always do
I knew all along
but this really is what her work is like
everyone's so grown up
so stylish
so hard at work
and Yamada is a part of it all
what am I even wearing
wow
macarons
for once you're done
what's wrong
all this just feels like
child's play all of a sudden
you're the one
who said you wanted to know her better
but
on second thought
this has nothing to do with me
you don't need to run away
but I'm not
oh really
then our feelings are just for play
go
why are you
because
I saw you running away
yeah but
aren't you working
it's okay
I told them I needed a bathroom break
what's wrong
do you feel sick
no
I'm fine
you should go back to your shoot
sorry
for what
this isn't
probably very fun for you
who cares
work isn't about being fun or not
you know
no
you think so
remember what I told you
before
about how I never got good
at the things I practiced
and I always quit
I felt the same way
about this job
huh
in the grand scheme of things
there are so many girls
who are cuter
prettier
better actors
and way funnier
than I could ever be
I get in trouble
every day
it's exhausting
I didn't really know
why I kept at it
but then you made me see
so you
like what you do
I was so happy
to hear that
Yamada is happy
so I should be too
so then
why does this hurt so much
if she doesn't go back
if she skips work
if she gets fired
if she
went back
to being just an ordinary
junior high girl
if she did
if that's all she was
I wouldn't have fallen
for her like this
there you are
took you long
what come on
they'll get the wrong idea
well now
you sure don't look like
any ordinary friend of Anna's
no
I uh
who is this guy
look at that build
and those terrifying eyes
this is
I mean
this is Ichikawa
really
him
is that so
here
her manager
a guy this stylish
you've got nice eyes
nope
nope nope nope
that's definitely a nope
I'll let you have one macaron
I'm good
thanks
it's a young junior high boy
you're correct
he most certainly is
you got an eight girl
Otsuki
I just want to revel
in that youth
Niko Koda is ready
Niko Koda
you don't know her
she's a cover model
for CL
and she's even on TV
what a striking face
oh my god Anna
you won't believe
what happened to me
the taxi driver
kept ignoring me
you're so cool
and collected
as always Anna
is she
this your son
do I look like a mom
yes yes yes
just like that
I really was imagining things
no one would see me
and Yamada like that
just because we were
side by side
can't wait to go home
no
you've got a massive
inferiority complex
I mean
I've been working with her
for four years now
I'm more like her guardian
really
and no one's as honest
as that girl
she tells me everything
even about you
matter of fact
I would go so far as to say
that you are her pride and joy
huh
that said
she's reaching an important stage
in her work
I assume you know
how your relationship
will hinder her performance
you understand right
what
hmm
wait
hang on a sec
what
but we
aren't
going out
or stuff
I swear I have an eye
for these things
is that what we really look like
well
but I really respect her
quite a lot
Anna I mean
more upfront than I thought
that's it
since way back then
ever since that moment
that's why it hurts
I hate how much of a child
I am
um
what did you think
today
um
quiet
but somehow intense
I was actually surprised
how many people are involved
no no
not all that stuff
I mean
uh
oh
I forgot
is this okay
is it creepy
I snuck in a picture too
if you're going to take one
take it when I look better
why
you look so pretty
huh
uh